and that class is why you must take a
gun with you if you are ever planning on
visiting Mexico you never know when some
crazy amigo is going to throw some tacos
at you or some [ __ ] I hope you children
are writing this down you're going to
need to know this stuff someday I'd hate
for one of you to get shot down because
you're wide
well Sonic did you draw that that's
really cool I didn't know you could draw
so well not only do you have the biggest
ass in school but you're so good at
drawing to that Picasso himself would
[ __ ] his pants if he saw your art thanks
to methey I'm planning to give it to my
boyfriend Bart Levy since tomorrow's
Valentine's Day oh yeah you're taping
that rich guy aren't you
I'm sure it will be the best present
ever big boy I hope he likes it it's
nothing compared to Alma gifts he's been
giving me today
[Music]
Robert did you make sure to give my
[ __ ] the best view possible of my
Valentine's message it has done sir it
was as clear as Sonic's love for a plate
of chili dogs and tater tots very good
then you may return back to base I'll
give you a raise of fifty eight billion
[ __ ] yet
on second thought I just realized that
there is a stain on that jet shoot it
down but Sir Johnson will be killed if
we shoot it down and objet cost you
eight billion dollars look like I give a
[ __ ]
I have 16,000 Jets just like that at
home I am not about to let one with a
huge goop stain land within 100 feet of
me I make myself clear or do I have to
kill you as well no I understand my
place master Bart levy
I'll inform someone to shoot that [ __ ]
down well fireworks - Bart levy really
went all out
sounds like that was the school Bell
it's a shame all you sweet boys and
girls can't stay longer you kids have a
wonderful Valentine's date tomorrow try
not to get into too much trouble and of
course if any of you sweet sweet boys
want me to be their Valentine all you
have to do is ask and daddy might just
say yes of course it'll be our secret yo
back the [ __ ] up there Mr. Jefferson
you're like 35
um hey hey there Sonia hell are you
doing I like your hair it's been quite
baloney II um hey there Billy what do
you want I'm getting ready to go home
with my brothers
you better not be asking me out on a
date again I already told you it's never
going to happen since you tried to rape
my bromantic well you see today's
Valentine's Day I was kind of hoping
that you might reconsider and I would
think that you would like a big strong
man like me to show off to all your
girlfriends come on Sonya
let's get out of here already I talked
with your uncle Chuck and he said your
family would give me a ride home today
oh okay sorry Billy I have to go now and
I'll have to decline your offer you're
just too ugly
so Billy Sun how did it go did you get
in the girls pants yet like I told you
to what do you think that she still
hates me for trying to rape her brother
maybe I should just give up trying to
win that thing [ __ ] affection she
will never love me what the [ __ ] are you
saying boy you and I both know that this
has nothing to do with love
this is about son ex-boyfriend Bart Levy
not that persona it's always been about
Bart levy but daddy
if you marry Sonya then he'll become the
stepbrother of Sonic the Hedgehog and
then when Sonic marries Bart levy will
be a part of the richest family alive
and then Billy your daddy will be the
happiest man alive because while
Bartleby loves Sonic instead of me I
will still be with him forever
do you understand Sonya is just a tool I
need to use to get closer to the man I
love to get closer to the man that was
stolen from me by one of my very own
students I trusted
but Dad I I really do love Sonia and if
she doesn't love me back
I don't want to force her I think it's
time you give up on your dream of
getting noticed by Bart Levy besides
you're married what would mom think if
she found out you were a [ __ ] what the
hell do you know do you have any idea
how long I've been planning this do you
know what I had to go through to make
sure you didn't get expelled after you
tried to rape Manic the Hedgehog I had
to let the principal spank my ass
[Music]
come on guys Uncle Chuck said he parked
the card on this side of school man
what's with everybody why is the parking
lot so crowded
maybe somebody famous is here hey guys
check that out over there
is it just me or does that look like a
pink limo you're right Manic I think
that is a pink limo it must be really
expensive I wonder whose it is
why hello there Beach I've been looking
all over for you
for me hehe is that so why on earth
would you be looking for me Bart levy
why so I could ask you to be my
Valentine of course
[Music]
Wow Knuckles isn't that soul romantic
I've Bart levy I sure wish somebody
would ask me to be their Valentine like
that instead of like you know give me
your useless Valentine's Day card or
some stupid [ __ ] mom we're back from
school
welcome back there our pizza rolls on
the table for you I just took them out
of the microwave so how was your day did
you learn anything interesting Oh before
I forget here Manic you wanted these
Valentine's Day cards didn't you there's
30 of them in the box that should be
enough for your whole classroom isn't
that right hell yeah thanks a lot mama
these are so [ __ ] bad-ass everyone's
going to love these bad boys ha ha ha
I'm glad you like them Manic be sure
that everyone gets one even that Billy
kid - no [ __ ] you in the Goddamn ass
[ __ ] he tried to rape me once why
should he get a Valentine from me he'll
probably just stick it up his butt Manek
I don't give a [ __ ] if he tried to bang
you in the ass you are not going to
embarrass our family yeah Andy you know
what Mel raising our kids for yoga class
so each way watching joke mama you just
tried asking Sonia out today tomorrow it
will be me what if Billy tries touching
my ass please mama I just know it he's
going to try slapping my butt ha ha ha
ha bro-bro oh you just hit my bro are
you ok my blue bro go stand in the
corner fat boy you're in timeout for the
next 15 minutes
ha ha ha ah ha ha ha you know you are
lucky I'm in a good mood today if I
wanted to I could just as easily have my
boyfriend Bart let me hire someone to
beat urs come on boys let's go have some
more of those cheeseburger flavored
pizza rolls
[Music]
oh great who's this now oh it's only the
mailman what do you want [ __ ] yeah uh I
got a package for miss alline are you
her by any chance flowers but I didn't
order anything like this there must be
some kind of mistake
well you know tomorrow is Valentine's
Day it seems as though you have a secret
admirer oh well I I can't really accept
these woman Elena
host accepting your own toy comedy one
daughter who is fairly no they did go
through the trouble sending it here I
guess it would be rude to just throw it
out I'll tell you what I would do miss
if some guy sent me flowers as beautiful
as those I would let him throw me on the
ground and [ __ ] my huge ass especially
if he had a moustache as awesome as your
brothers is haha you guys have fun now I
have more mail to deliver so what should
we do should we send these back hey wait
a minute why do these flowers smell like
beer
Charles be honest with me did you have
all neighbor dress up as a mailman just
so you could send me flowers and make me
think you're cool or something what
Norway you all never Domingo that you're
in Charles I know what you're doing and
I want it to stop that was obviously our
neighbour and II know you all said it
that way only Logan Rika Randy is that
so then why is he going into Randy's
house is probably host Arabist
talent or appear and this gives is it
with the act Charles and not letting you
touch my ass
[Music]
Randy Brandi are you Terry hey Charles
how did the plan go are you banging that
[ __ ] in the ass yet haha Randy in a Leo
thought that I can't be a tornado will
kill sweetie window huh
but why I'm already in my whitey
tighties and getting ready for bed
come on man who's done enjoyed if a Yeti
only carries him fine I suppose I can do
that but I'm expecting double in payment
yeah yeah who's Domingo it Ilan Pino all
along he did welcome for all it so it
looks like we doing this thing keep you
eyes on the window hey son can I see you
for a moment please
yet sure thing daddy what for what for
hope that that's a secret my son like a
surprise oh boy idle of surprise it is
it a trip to Disney World daddy
or are we going out for ice cream hey
daddy have I ever told you how much I
love you I I love you too my son now
come let's go
[Music]
he clearly inna loco birthday at the
window oh [ __ ] he has Randy his son with
him maybe it really wasn't Randy at all
oh no he is a belt he's going to be -
[Music]
bro get over here and help us sort out
these Valentine carts for class tomorrow
bro are you listening to me you better
not be writing fanfics about you and
Bart Levy again guys you might want to
come and check this [ __ ] out and I mean
now what's the deal Sonic
do you got anything interesting you want
to show us take a look for yourself my
homeboy what it's just an ordinary oh my
God it's that [ __ ] Billy from our
class he has a Twitter and that's not
all
take a look at what he said about you
bro look right here in his bio he said
you like big and sweaty ball sex no it's
not true
I do not like big-ass balls are you
telling me the world can see this look
right there this was just posted an hour
ago are you [ __ ] me he's posing with
a gun and telling people not to come to
school seriously that is messed up that
could actually scare someone not cool at
all
hold up what's that stain on his butt
did he poop himself haha I don't think
he even noticed bro give me the computer
for a second why what are you going to
do I'm going to teach him a lesson
you two just watch
laughing out loud oh [ __ ] Manic you
insane hey wait what the hell why is the
web page being reloaded
oh my God Billy took down the image haha
he really pooped in his pants it's too
bad he took it down though I wanted to
look at it some more don't worry dude
check this out
oh my God bro since you saved that and
put it back up the whole world can see
that now there's nothing Billy can do
about it hahahaha
son how many times do we have to go
through this the Internet is meant to be
used for reading Sonic the Hedgehog's
veronik fanfics not so you can try and
show off on Twitter
do I have to spank you to get you to
understand the Internet bill was 60
cents more than last month's we must
take priorities if we want to keep this
house so stop being stupid or well
what's done is done I will just beat you
tomorrow before school break up and get
in bed [ __ ] I need to get some beauty
Sleet
like Bartleby does okay but Dad do you
always have to wear that Sonic the
Hedgehog beanie cap to bed at night are
you trying to sass me boy that's it I'm
taking away your laptop tomorrow now get
in bed oh and you can say goodbye to
your allowance too don't you [ __ ] with
me gays you're barred lemme wig do I
have to dad it itches do you want me to
beat your ass
yeah baby now that's hot
hey sis have you seen Manic anywhere huh
I thought he was with you did he ditch
school again everybody checked that out
now what's going on over there check
that out that green kid just at Jesus
Christ
he's staring on all of the haters did
you guys see that I wish I was as cool
as him so sugar tits will you be my
special Valentine
Dominic yes of course I will Goddamn
Manic that was slick Thanks
I know how to handle a [ __ ] with a big
butt and boobs now let's get on to class
already it seems like ladies are already
lining up to give me Valentine cookies
all righty class now that the test is
over you may now pass around Valentine's
if you have any and like I said
yesterday if any of you sexy boys and
girls have anything to give me please do
so hey Sonic do me a favor and give this
to your sister will you I don't think I
want to what the [ __ ] do you mean you
don't want to [ __ ] it's not like I'm
asking you to suck my balls what kind of
game are you playing here to maken man
my sweet sister would never accept a
Valentine's gift from you I would never
allow it I never said it was a
Valentine's Day gift Fat Boy my great
grandfather a fair the Great Sage LT
Echidna just made too many cookies so
I'm handing these sweet little [ __ ]
out to the class fine I'll give them to
her I guess I'm going to go take a [ __ ]
hey they're Manic um I saw you riding up
to school today on your skateboard I
didn't know you were so talented you
know I had a thing for bad boys like you
I thought it was so cool how you [ __ ]
your [ __ ] pants but didn't give any
bucks what can I say ladies
my motto is you can poop anywhere at any
time you just got to be able to own it
you know they used to call me the poster
in fifth grade okay happy Valentine's
Day Sonia here are tickets for you Sonic
and Matt for the strip club down the
street I'm going to be pole dancing
there this weekend thanks Mindy but I
thought you were banned from there for
taking all your clothes off last time
actually I was banned for having sex
with about 42 people at the same time
but I am going to try sneaking in
through the back if I get caught well
I'm sure the manager will let me see if
I let in bang me in the S six or seven
times hey Sonia Knuckles wanted me to
give you this empty basket okay um but
why I don't remember I think he said
something about pooping in it
hey Manic um I saw the comment you left
on my Twitter last night
about the poop stain please don't tell
the rest of the class I'm still wearing
those same pants I know it smells like
[ __ ] over here
but my family is poor we don't have
money for more pants that's not why I'm
here Billy happy Valentine's Day big boy
but Manic I tried to rape you one time
do you really not hate me anymore
Billy my Uncle Chuck always taught me
you don't fight fire with sparks you
fight fire with love if you spend your
whole life hating somebody a piece of
you will always be in the darkness
[Music]
please Billy turn the card over there is
something special I've written down for
you on the back
[Music]
[Laughter]
What's Wrong Billy you were the one who
posted the image online for the public
to see I thought you wanted everybody to
see it
[Music]
good job bro I didn't think you had it
in you
you really showed that [ __ ] what
happens when you mess with a Hedgehog
family something tells me that Billy
won't be bothering any of us ever again
everybody gives you inside
[Music]
[Applause]